<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY % BOOK_ENTITIES SYSTEM "Deployment_Guide.ent">
%BOOK_ENTITIES;
]>
<chapter id="chap-Deployment_Guide-Deployment_Scenarios">
    <title>Deployment Scenarios</title>
    <para>
        Depending on the target use of Cyrus IMAP, different features and architectures may be used to make optimal use of the Cyrus IMAP features. This chapter briefly touches different deployment scenarios.
    </para>
    <section id="sect-Deployment_Guide-Deployment_Scenarios-Single_Server_Deployments">
        <title>Single Server Deployments</title>
        <para>
            In a deployment scenario with a single server, use this checklist to make sure you get the right scalability and functionality;
        </para>
        <para>
            <itemizedlist>
                <listitem>
                    <para>
                        In the foreseeable future, might this deployment run for multiple domain name spaces?
                    </para>

                </listitem>
                <listitem>
                    <para>
                        Is this deployment going to close in on it's maximum capacity?
                    </para>

                </listitem>
                <listitem>
                    <para>
                        Is high-availability required?
                    </para>

                </listitem>

            </itemizedlist>

        </para>
        <para>
            If the answer to all of these questions is a consistent no, then please continue with the Installation Guide.
        </para>

    </section>

    <section id="sect-Deployment_Guide-Deployment_Scenarios-Multi_Server_Deployments">
        <title>Multi Server Deployments</title>
        <para>
            This is a test paragraph in a section
        </para>

    </section>

    <section id="sect-Deployment_Guide-Deployment_Scenarios-Cyrus_Murder">
        <title>Cyrus Murder</title>
        <para>
            This is a test paragraph in a section
        </para>

    </section>

    <section id="sect-Deployment_Guide-Deployment_Scenarios-Cyrus_Replication">
        <title>Cyrus Replication</title>
        <para>
            This is a test paragraph in a section
        </para>

    </section>

    <section id="sect-Deployment_Guide-Deployment_Scenarios-Hosted_Environments">
        <title>Hosted Environments</title>
        <para>
            This is a test paragraph in a section
        </para>

    </section>

    <section id="sect-Deployment_Guide-Deployment_Scenarios-Mailbox_Creation_Distribution">
        <title>Mailbox Creation Distribution</title>
        <para>
            By default, when creating a mailbox in Cyrus IMAP:
        </para>
        <para>
            <itemizedlist>
                <listitem>
                    <para>
                        the backend with the most free disk space is selected on the Murder frontend
                    </para>

                </listitem>
                <listitem>
                    <para>
                        the partition with the most free disk space is selected on the backend
                    </para>

                </listitem>

            </itemizedlist>

        </para>
        <para>
            This may not be the most appropriate backend or partition to create the new mailbox on, and Cyrus IMAP therefor allows for a variety of additional modes of calculating and selecting the most appropriate backend and partition. The exact mode for the selection is controlled with the <filename>imapd.conf</filename> setting <literal>serverlist_select_mode</literal> on the frontend and <literal>partition_select_mode</literal> on the backend.
        </para>
        <para>
            Alternatively, a default backend can be configured with the <literal>defaultserver</literal> setting on a frontend, and a default partition can be configured with the <literal>defaultpartition</literal> on a backend.
        </para>
        <para>
            As usual, details and guidelines are available in the Administrator Guide and the Configuration Reference.
        </para>
        <remark>Make the remark above a general one, and provide a link to the administrator guide and configuration reference ? (how ?) </remark>

    </section>


</chapter>

